[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":27622,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":33040,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure tha t when w e combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":3788,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":36830,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":10150,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":46981,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1501,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":48482,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0 .3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3529,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":52012,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":819,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":52832,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result .)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["6","0"],"rt":8135,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":60968,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1009,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":61979,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3054,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":65033,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 beca use 1 +  1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":796,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":65829,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2527,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":68356,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1020,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":69377,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first num ber, and  then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2689,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":72066,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":759,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":72826,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3433,"trial_type":"qu estion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":76260,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":779,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":77040,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2922,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":79963,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":756,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":80720,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2571,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":83292,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":981,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":84274,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get yo ur resul t.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2762,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":87036,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1573,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":88611,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":13494,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":102106,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":234425,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":336533,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3618,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":340151,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":973,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":341126,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2302,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":343429,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":859,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":344288,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse  of 3 und er +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2431,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":346721,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":789,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":347510,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2163,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":349673,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":656,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":350330,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3231,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":353562,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2412,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":355975,"internal_chunk_id":"0 -0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":7994,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":363969,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> How ever, 2  is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":57259,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":421228,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":7556,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":428787,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1050,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":429837,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2157,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":431995,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":3177,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":435172,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub> ? <br /> <br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":2116,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":437289,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":829,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":438119,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":14446,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":452567,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":887,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":453455,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining  question s as accurately as possible.","rt":9347,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":462802,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3547,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":466349,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":836,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":467185,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2923,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":470109,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"fre e","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3771,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":473881,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3314,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":477196,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3445,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":480643,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":18646,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":499289,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5 - 4+1 is less than 9","response_history":["4","5 - 4+1 is less than 9"],"rt":11045,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":510335,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3 - added 8+4 then subtracted 9","response_history":["3 - added 8+4 then subtracted 9"],"rt":17378,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":527714,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0 -  sorry,  I don't remember the specific reason","response_history":["0 - nr","0 - n","0 - because","0 - becaus","0 - becau","0 - beca","0 - bec","0 - be","0 - b","0 - sorry, I don't remember the specific reason"],"rt":59596,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":587310,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":8288,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":595599,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":2645,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":598245,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","response_history":["9"],"rt":3197,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":601443,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6 - it makes 9 when added to 3","response_history":["6 0 ","6 0","6 - it makes 9 when added to 3"],"rt":12149,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":613593,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no, because it does not make all the other generators","response_history":["no, because it does not make all the other generators"],"rt":10481,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":624075,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no - because it does not make all the other generators","response_history":["no - because it does not make all the other generators"],"rt":10337,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":634413,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes, because it makes the other generators","response_history":["yes, because it makes the other generators"],"rt":7799,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":642213,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</ sub>? Pl ease explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no, because it does not make the other generators","response_history":["no, because it does not make the other generators"],"rt":7998,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":650213,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":6554,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":656767,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n- 1","response":"1 + n0","response_history":["1 + n0"],"rt":11015,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":667783,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"I don't know","response_history":["I don't know"],"rt":8194,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":675977,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I don't know","response_history":["I don't know"],"rt":9090,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":685069,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4096,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":689165,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":5015,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":694181,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":10251,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":704433,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"No, because that does not make sense","response_history":["I don't ","I don't","No, because that does not make sense"],"rt":14320,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":718754,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":5022,"trial_type":"questio n","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":723777,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"Sometimes - depends on the numbers","response_history":["Sometimes - depends on the numbers"],"rt":12199,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":735978,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":6457,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":742437,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1470,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":743908,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"30","response_history":["30"],"rt":6096,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":750005,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":2096,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":752101,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Basic math course in college for non-math/science majors","response_history":["Intermediate Aleb","Intermediate Alegb","Intermediate Aleg","Basic math course in college for on","Basic math course in college for o","Basic math course in college for non-math/science majors"],"rt":23815,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":775917,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 -  used it,  remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3457,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":779375,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":2414,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":781791,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - som ewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3178,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":784970,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3994,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":788965,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":2488,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":791454,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":2104,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":793559,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":7271,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":800831,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"","response_history":[],"rt":224,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":801055,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Thank y ou!","response_history":["Thank you!"],"rt":6156,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":807211,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]